# RAYMOND CHUNG

Archung95.github.io ≥12rc51@queensu.ca in raymondchung95 € prchung95

# **SUMMARY:**

I am a developer from Toronto, ON with a love for programming, sports and people. I specialize on Front End Development, UI/UX Design and teaching with an emphasis on usability and relentless attention to detail and visual execution.



### EDUCATION

# **Queen's University**

Computer Science (Honours) Graduating May 2017

### **Queen's University**

Concurrent Education Graduating May 2018



### **SKILLS**

### Languages:

Proficient in Python, HTML,

Familiar with Java, PHP. JavaScript, Swift2

### **Technologies:**

Proficient with Bash, Git, Bootstrap Familiar with AngularJS, ¡Query, Node.js + Express

#### Design:

Proficient with Photoshop, Illustrator Familiar with Sketch3, Affinity Design

#### Interests:

Education, Basketball, Cooking, Soccer

# **ACTIVITIES**

- Incoming IT Coordinator of Queen's Startup Summit (2016-2017)
- Member of Software Developer's Club (2016-Present)
- Peer Tutor of a variety of Computer Science courses (2014-Present)

# **EXPERIENCE**

## Research Assistant, Queen's University

May 2016 - Present

- Researching the execution and analysis of UML models to help maximize the potential of Model-Driven Development
- Debugged and improved a URM toolkit used to teach software modelling

# Web Developer, COMPSA Web Services

July 2015 - Present

- Develop and maintain websites for student-run clubs and organization using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and Bootstrap
- Design websites using Adobe Photoshop

### **Teaching Assistant**, Queen's University

Jan 2016 - April 2016

- Led CISC P81: Computers: Applications & Implications
- Proctored, assisted and graded over 90 tests and weekly lab assignments in a consistent and timely manner

#### Co-Founder. Foody Co

Sept 2016 - April 2016

- Launched a subscription-based healthy meal service targeted towards students
- Responsible for creating and maintaining the website

# </> PROJECTS

### **Application Portal**, Web Application

- Created an application portal Queen's Startup Summit to make the delegation process more efficient and effective and to handle over 100 applications
- Built using the MEAN stack (MongoDb, Express, AngularJs and Node.js)

### **DeckLog App.** Android

- App that tracks the user's location and logs down the distance travelled and average sailing speed: made for and use by Kingston's Redwood Power & Sail club
- Responsible for the design and front-end of the app
- Developed using Android studio, with SQLite as backend and Adobe Photoshop for design